Rachna ji, good morning. Rachna ji, your pick for today is
good morning and my pick for today will be
Indian Hotels, which we will
try to play on the long side. We will
talk about June futures naturally and
here we are sitting at 67 as per the futures.
We will place SL in it at 657
and will go long in futures for
a target of upside at 675 and 685
Indus Tower and Indian Hotels
Picks till now Bahti saheb Good morning Today's top
call Bhai saheb
Good morning Ashish ji Good morning Anuj
ji Good morning everyone Ashish ji ICICI
GI Buying advice would be given on this ICICI
LBA General Insurance The insurance as a
space is looking quite attractive and
we had given recommendation in ICICI in Friday's session as well
and after that a
strong move was made and in yesterday's session also
follow through buying is being seen very strong.
So shopping can be done here.  The
stop loss to be maintained in this should be
maintained at 1820 and SL at 18820.   The
levels of the targets that will be above can be seen up to 1890, 1890 and 1930.
Ok.  Now let's go to Amit Seth